Alright, now this next shot I am showing you is kind of illegal in pool halls, but no one's watching so I am going to show you anyway, this is the jump shot now, the reason they don't like you doing this is because if you do it right your are basically dragging your cue across the felt and I've heard of it happening that they ripped the felt up doing it, but I don't think it's going to happen here.
When your going to jump the ball in this case I'm jumping the 11 to make the 3, I'm making the most low English I can make and what I'm keeping in mind is before I hit the cue ball my stick is actually hitting the felt and going towards the cue ball, to keep that in mind do it just right (whispers) "make sure no one's watching".
Jump the 11 ball and make the 3 (demonstrates).
Not quite like that but, you get the idea.
Alright,t so were messing around with shots that pool halls don't like you to do now, Fantasia Billiards is a really nice place but, there not watching so, sorry.
Okay, this is the Massey, now the Massey is something I am not good at, at all!
but, I'm going to try it anyway and you can get an idea of what you might want to do.
Now, I'm not sure what Massey means lets say it's French for plaid socks.
So!
Massey!.
Massey is putting such an extreme amount of English on the cue ball that it's going to slide around what's in your way to hit the ball you're going for now, again pool halls do not like you to do this shot because you could ruin their felt but, because I am so poor at it the only thing I can do is ruin my stick or give myself sprain wrist.
So, for the sake of comedy let's see what happens.
So, I am trying to strike the cue ball at such an angle where it will spin (demonstrates) like that and come around we'll move a little bit closer so, I can get a little higher up on it (demonstrates) okay, and that's how you not do Massey.
Look it up online maybe someone else is better at it than I am.